A Guide to the Russell Sage Foundation records, SG 3 FA413
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1965-2016; 1; 48.23 Cubic Feet 127 letter document boxes
  - Cultural Contact
    - Bendick and Egan - Understanding Employment Discrimination in its Workplace Context (87-02-07), 2001-2007 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Bourgois - Confronting Inner City Social Suffering: Teaching Doctors to Heal Poverty (83-01-03), 2003-2005 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Britto - "Man Ana" - An Investigation of Ethnic Identity Formation of Muslim Arab Children in the U.S. (87-06-04), 2006-2010 (Box 12, Folder 3-5)
    - Burk - Critical Review of Theoretical Propositions and Empirical Research about Race Relations in the U.S. Army (87-08-06), 2008-2010 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Cohen - Identity Threat and the Racial Achievement Gap (87-08-02), 2007-2011 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Dawson - Race and Civil Society (87-02-03), 2001-2005 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Dempsey and Wilson - The U.S. Army on the Civil Rights Frontier since World War II (87-08-05), 2008-2010 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Dobbin - Diversity Programs at Work: Corporate Activities and Workforce Composition (87-02-03), 2001-2007 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Dovidio - Immigration and National Belonging (87-11-03), 2011-2013 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Eberhardt - Policing Racial Bias (87-04-05), 2004-2008 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Fernandez - Immigration, Culture and Health Care (87-07-02), 2006-2013 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Fiske - Envy Up and Contempt Down - Intergroup Experience in the Stereotype Content Model (87-08-03), 2007-2011 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Fuligni - Social Identification and the Academic Adaptation of Adolescents from Immigrant Families (87-05-02), 2004-2009 (Box 38, Folder 1-2)
    - Good - How Does Culture Make a Difference in American Health Care - American Health at the Interface of Ethnicity/Race and Citizenship (87-05-03), 2005-2010 (Box 41, Folder 4, Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Goff - Conference to Clarify Research Priorities, Methods, and a Timeline for Working with Law Enforcement Agencies (87-09-03), 2009-2010 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Goff - Policing Inequality - Building an Agenda for Research on Racial Bias in Law Enforcement (87-10-02), 2007-2013 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Goff - Policing Inequality - Building an Agenda for Research on Racial Bias in Policing (87-13-04), 2013-2015 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Goff - Policing Equity - Scaffolding the Future of Racial and Gender Equity Research in Law Enforcement (87-12-03), 2011-2013 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Hopkins - Perceived Discrimination among Immigrants as a Function of Community-Level Variables (87-12-01), 2011-2013 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Hopkins, Kaiser, Perez - Perceptions of Discrimination and the Acquisition of Partisan Identity in Immigrant Communities (87-14-05), 2014-2015 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Hu - Under the Knife - Medical Noncompliance in Among Immigrants (87-06-03), 2006-2010 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Humphreys - Assessing Strategies to Combat Housing Discrimination in New York City - A Field Experiment (87-13-02), 2012-2015 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Katz - Family Trials - Immigrant Generation and Latino's Experiences Managing the Bronx Family Court System (87-14-06), 2013-2015 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Keltner - Interracial Friendship (87-03-05), 2003-2010 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Kira - Trauma Related Factors and Socio-Cultural Acceptance in a Group of Iraqi Refugees (87-05-05), 2004-2009 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Kryson - Changing Terrain of Race and Ethnicity - Theory, Methods, and Public Policy (87-02-01), 2001-2005 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Le - School Context and Developmental Patterns of Delinquency and Violence among Immigrant Youth (87-08-04), 2008-2011 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Legewie - Racial Profiling in Stop-and-Frisk Operations - Do Local Events Trigger Periods of Increased Discrimination (87-14-03), 2014-2016 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - London-Thompson and Rajaram - Minority Status and the Academic Achievement Gap - Assessment of the Social, Cognitive, and Health Markers of Stereotype Threat (87-07-03), 2007-2012 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Mallett and Wilson - Affective Forecasting - Implications for Outgroup Contact (87-05-04), 2005-2010 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Markus - From Diversity to Community - Models of Difference and Inclusion in American Life - Phase Two (87-02-11), 2002-2006 (Box 72, Folder 4, Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Marrow - Social Status and Qualities of Intergroup Contact among Immigrants and Natives (87-12-02), 2011-2014 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Markus - From Diversity to Community - Models of Difference and Inclusion in American Life (87-00-05), 2000-2006 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Matsuo - Functional Fitness, Psychological Well-Being, and Intercultural Identity in Cross-Cultural Adaptation (87-06-02), 2006-2010 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Medin - Cognitive Mediation of Indigenous and Non-Indigenous Conflict Over a Shared Environment (87-99-02), 2001-2004 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Muckenge - Socio-Cultural Factors in Diet, Nutrition, and Health - Comparing African Immigrant and African American Families in Atlanta (87-08-01), 2007-2008 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Murray - The Relationship Between Police Officers' Racial Attitudes and Their On-the-Job Behavior (87-06-05), 2006-2009 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Mutz - Obama as Exemplar - Effects of Mediated Intergroup Contact (87-11-01), 2010-2014 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Najdowski - Effect of Citizen's Response to Stereotype Threat of Police Officers' Perceptions and Decision Making (87-13-05), 2013-2014 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Park, Bernadette - Unconscious Racial Biases in Police Decision Making (87-03-06), 2003-2008 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Ricento - Language Ecology and Health Care - Language Varieties and Communication in a Latino-Serving Family Health Center (87-07-01), 2006-2008 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Ruble and Eccles - Social Identity in Context - Behavioral Engagement and Commitment to Educational and Other Institutions (87-03-02), 2005-2007 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Shweder - Ethnic Customs, Assimilation and American Law (87-98-02), 1999-2002 (Box 108, Folder 2, Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Shweder - Law and Culture - Engaging Differences in Everyday Setting (87-00-06), 2000-2003 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Shweder - Law and Culture Working Group (87-02-12), 2002-2008 (Box 110, Folder 2-3, Box 111, Folder 1-3)
    - Sidanius - Studies in Intergroup Conflict - A University Context (87-95-04), 1995-2010 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Shweder - The Qur'an and the Constitution - Islamic Adaptations in the United States (87-02-09), 2002-2008 (Box 114, Folder 3, Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Sommers - Evaluating Diversity - The Influence of Racial and Gender Composition on Information Processing and Group Decision Making (87-06-01), 2006-2009 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Sommers - Understanding and Improving Students' Experiences in Racially Diverse College Settings (87-09-01), 2008-2013 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Stewart - Consider the Situation - Reducing Intergroup Bias Through Attribution Training (87-09-02), 2009-2013 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Tyler, Tom - Legitimacy, Accountability, and Social Order - Majority and Minority Community Perspectives on the Law and Legal Authorities (87-02-10), 2001-2007 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Windsor - Methods to Evaluate Social Work Courses about Oppression, Diversity, and Social Justice (87-10-01), 2009-2011 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Woodzicka - The Measurement and Intergroup Impact of White Privilege (87-04-03), 2004-2008 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Elite Influence
    - Kogut - The Political Coloring of Corporate Boards - Directors and the Ideological Slant of Corporate Interests (83-13-16), 2013-2015 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Future of Work
    - Acemoglu - The Transformation of Work and the Labor Market (85-01-10), 2000-2007 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - Appelbaum and Batt - Private Equity at Work (85-12-01), 2012-2015 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Applebaum and Milkman - Work-Family Policy In California - Understanding Employers' Experiences with Paid Family Leave (85-09-07), 2009-2011 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Batt - The Global Call Center Research Project - An International Comparison of Low-Wage Service Workers (85-03-06), 2003-2009 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Batt, Hunter and Wilk - The Quality of Jobs and Mobility Opportunities for the Customer Service and Sales Workers (85-99-04), 1998-2009 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Batt and Liebman - Working Group on Franchising and Low Wage Work, 2014 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Bartel, Ichniowski and Shaw - Impact of Workplace and Technological Innovations on the Demand for Less-Skilled Labor - A study of three industries (85-99-08), 1999-2008 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Batt - Global Call Center Research Project, Part II - An International Comparison of Low Wage Service Workers (85-05-02), 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
    - Bernhardt and Heckathorn - Documenting Unregulated Work: A Survey of Workplace Violations in NYC (85-06-04), 2005-2009 (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
    - Bernhardt and DeFilippis - Off the Radar Screen - Unregulated Jobs in Chicago and NYC - Phase Two (85-05-07), 2005-2007 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Bosch and Weinkopf - Low-wage Work in Germany (85-04-06), 2004-2008 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Brenner - Evaluating the Economic Impact of Boston's Living Wage Ordinance (85-04-01), 2003-2006 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Cappelli - A Study of the Extent of and Potential Causes of Alternative Employment Arrangements (85-01-24), 2000-2009 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Care Work Policy Briefs (85-09-04), 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Folbre - Care Work Working Group Years 2-4 Appropriation (85-11-01), 2011-2014 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Caroli and Ashkenazy - Low-Wage Work in France (85-04-08), 2004-2009 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Carre and Tilly - Continuity and Change in Low-Wage Work in Retail Trade in the U.S. (85-05-03), 2004-2008 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Charles and England - Who Cares - Intergenerational Transmission and Determinants of Working in Care Occupations (85-12-05), 2010-2013 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Cherlin - The Polarization of Family Formation and of the Labor Market - Are They Related (85-112-08), 2012-2014 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Duncan - Non-Cognitive Skills and Labor Market Outcomes (85-96-12), 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Irons and Mishel - The Social Costs of Long-Term Unemployment, 85-10-02, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - England, Budig, and Kahn - Penalties for Paid and Unpaid Care Work (85-11-03), 2011-2015 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Fairlie - Race, Families and Success in Small Business: A Comparison of African American, Asian, and White-Owned Businesses (85-05-01), 2004-2008 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - RSF - The Social Organization of Care Work Provision (85-09-06), 2009-2015 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Freeman - Shared Capitalism Research Project (85-00-14), 2001-2012 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Grogger - The Effects of Trade and Immigration on Low-Skill Workers - Revisiting the Issues with a Cohort of Labor Market Entrants, 85-07-06, 2007-2009 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Houseman - The Consequences of Temporary Agency Employment for Low-Skilled Workers (85-06-01), 2005-2013 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Jacobs - The Workforce Linkages of Community Colleges (85-01-12), 2000-2006 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Johnson, Susan - A Study of New Teachers' Experiences of Hiring (5-02-03), 2001-2005 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Jones, Derek - Changing Employment Practices and the Quality of Jobs - Case Studies of Medium Size Firms in Metropolitan and Non-Metropolitan Communities in Central New York (85-00-02), 1999-2006 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Kim - Black Women and Double Discrimination in Employment (85-08-03), 2007-2011 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Kochan - Employment Policy Research Network (85-10-04), 2010-2012 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Kuttner - Special Issue of The American Prospect (85-03-07), 2003-2006 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - LaLonde-George - Employment Transitions and Family Formation of Female Ex-Offenders (85-03-02), 2004-2007 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Lambert - Improving Scheduling in Entry-Level Retail Jobs - A Workplace-Based Experiment (85-06-02), 2006-2010 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Leana - The Effects of Employment-Status Congruence, Worksite Context and Formalization on Caregiver and Care Recipient Outcomes in Long-Term Care (85-11-04), 2011-2015 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Leete, Dresser, and Pastor - Economic Opportunity in a Volatile Economy - Understanding the Role of Labor Market Intermediaries in Two Regions (85-99-11), 2001-2007 (Box 64, Folder 3-4)
    - Lefranc - Parental Background, Educational Attainment and Labor Market Outcomes in France (83-09-16), 2009-2010 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Levy - Seminar Series on the Labor Market Effects of Computerized Work (85-14-02), 2013-2016 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Levy - Is College Still Worth It (85-12-10), 2012-2013 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - RSF - Low-Wage Work in Europe and the United States - Phase II (85-06-05), 2006-2010 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Marcotte - The Economic Returns to Education, 2002-2008 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Mason - International Benchmarking Study of Low-Wage Employment (85-07-03), 2007-2009 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Mason - Low-Wage Work in the United Kingdom (85-04-09), 2004-2008 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - RSF - Meetings to Coordinate the Case Studies of Job Quality (85-05-05), 2005-2010 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - RSF - Meetings to Develop a Russell Sage Working Group on Care Work (85-09-02), 2008-2010 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - RSF - What Explains Their Involvement - American Employers Associations and Workforce Development Initiatives (85-02-04), 2008-2010 (Box 78, Folder 4-5)
    - The Andrew Mellon Foundation Grant to RSF for Literacy Admin., 1994-2002 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Meyers - Old Assumptions, New Realities - Economic Security for Working Families in the 21st Century (85-08-04), 2008-2010 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Morin - Adapting to Workplace Technological Change over the Long Run - Evidence from US Longitudinal Data (85-15-12), 2015-2016 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Neumark - The School-to-Work Transition and School-to-Work Programs (85-03-08), 2004-2007 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Newman - The Long Run Careers of Low-Wage Workers - Next Steps for Research (85-02-05), 2001-2007 (Box 88, Folder 3-4)
    - Olson, Craig - Unions and the Labor Market (85-98-03), 1997-2005 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Osterman - Skill and Hiring in American Manufacturing (85-12-09), 2012-2013 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Osterman - A Good Jobs Nation (85-09-03), 2009-2013 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Orland - Workshop on Research Evidence Related to Future Skill Demands (85-07-02), 2006-2008 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Pager - Race, Gender, and the Supply-Side Dynamics of Labor Market Placement (85-13-01), 2013-2015 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Pattillo - Impact of Incarceration on Families and Communities (85-02-10), 2002-2007 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Persky - Impacts of the Illinois Minimum Wage: Employment, Hours and Labor Substitution in the Fast Food Industry (85-05-04), 2004-2010 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Pettit - Incarceration and Earnings Inequality - Evidence from Washington State (85-01-20), 2001-2007 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - RSF - Public Relations Campaign for the Future of Work Case Studies Volume (85-03-05), 2003-2004 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Rauch - Working Group on the Formation and Decay of Economic Networks (85-02-13), 2002-2008 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Rodgers - Decent Work, Social Policy and Development (85-07-01), 2006-2007 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Sabol - Effects of Access to Jobs, Neighborhood Characteristics and Prison Experiences on Offender Employment and Recidivism Outcomes (85-01-06), 2000-2004 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Salvedara and Van Klaveren - Low-Wage Work in The Netherlands (85-04-10), 2004-2008 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Salzman - The Social Transformation of Private Security Workforces (85-02-07), 2002-2005 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Salzman - The Dynamics of Internal Labor Market Evolution (85-98-10), 1999-2003 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Schmitt - The Employment Impact of City Minimum Wage Increases (85-07-04), 2007-2010 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Schreur - Rethinking Unemployment Insurance - Before the Next Recession (85-15-09), 2009-2015 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Sennett - The Council for a Civil Society - Planning Meetings (85-96-21), 1996-2002 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Stoll - The Effect of Criminal Background Checks on Hiring of Ex-Offenders (85-05-06), 2005-2007 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Stoll and Raphael - The Increasing Prison Population in the United States - What Has it Done for Us and What Has it Done to Us (85-06-03), 2006-2009 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Stone - Employment Regulation after the Demise of the Standard Employment Contract (85-10-03), 2010-2013 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Temin - Inequality and Institutions in 20th Century America (85-08-05), 2008-2010 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Tomaskovic-Devey - Building Research Capacity with the US Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (85-13-02), 2013-2015 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - RSF - Travel and Lodging Costs to Future of Work Researchers for the Labor Employment Relations Association (LERA) Annual Meeting (85-08-01), 2007-2009 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - RSF - Expenses for Members of the Opportunity in the Workplace - A United States Europe Comparison Research Team to Attend the 2009 SASE Annual Meeting (85-09-05), 2007-2009 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Tyler, John - Offender Re-Integration into the Mainstream Labor Market (85-00-16), 2000-2010 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Weill - Examining the Underpinnings of Labor Standards Compliance in Low-Wage Industries (85-08-06), 2008-2012 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Westergard-Nielson - Low-Wage Work in Denmark (85-04-07), 2004-2008 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Great Recession
    - Blinder, Lo, and Solow - Rethinking the Financial System (92-10-02), 2010-2013 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Bugard and Seefeldt - Recessionary Events and their Relationship to Health - Evidence from the Michigan Recession and Recovery Study (92-11-08), 2011-2014 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Campbell - Dire Straits - Fiscal Effects and Policy Choices During the Great Recession (92-12-03), 2011-2014 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Ellen, Been, and Chan - The Six Trillion Dollar Loss of Housing Wealth in the Great Recession - What are the Long Term Consequences (92-11-09), 2010-2013 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Enns - The Great Recession and State Criminal Justice Policy - Explaining the Unexpected (92-12-13), 2012-2015 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Evans - The Great Recession and Public Education (92-11-10), 2011-2015 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Garfinkel - The Great Recession, Family, Functioning, and Child Well-Being (92-13-01), 2012-2014 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - RSF - Great Recession Working Conferences (92-12-18), 2012-2015 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Greenfield - The Effects of the Great Recession on Young People's Values and Beliefs (92-12-04), 2011-2015 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Gross - The Great Recession and Fringe Banking - Has the Economic Crisis Transformed Financial Behavior (92-12-05), 2011-2016 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Grusky - The Social Consequences of the Great Recession, (92-10-01), 2010-2011 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Grusky - Project Proposal for Recession Trends Website (92-11-04), 2010-2011 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Hartmann - Low-Wage Women and the Great Recession (92-12-11), 2011-2013 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Johnson, Richard - The Financial Crisis, the Great Recession, and Retirement Security (92-11-11), 2011-2015 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Kalil - The Great Recession and Married Parents' Use of Time, 92-11-12, 2011-2013 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Kovak - Immigration, Internal Migration, and Local Labor Market Adjustment Following the U.S. Housing Bust (92-12-06), 2011-2014 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Larson - The Unemployed during the Great Recession: Policy Research on Social Science Safety (92-12-12), 2011-2012 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Manza and Brooks - Response and Non-Response of the American Public to the Great Recession (92-11-13), 2011-2013 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - McCarty - The Political Economy of Public Pension Funding (92-12-14), 2012-2015 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - McInerney - Consequences of the Great Recession on Health and Health-Related Outcomes (92-12-10), 2011-2015 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - McKernan - Wealth Loss during the Great Recession - Facts, Impacts, and Policy Reminders (92-11-14), 2011-2014 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Moffitt - The Great Recession and the Social Safety Net (92-11-15), 2011-2015 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Munnell - What is the Long-Term Impact of State Retirement Programs on State Fiscal Health in the Wake of the Economic Crisis (92-12-07), 2012-2013 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Munnell - The Impact of the Economic Crisis on Older Workers and Retirement Security (92-11-03), 2010-2012 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Painter - Caught in the Housing Bubble - Immigrants' Housing Outcomes in Traditional Gateways and Newly Emerging Destinations (92-11-02), 2009-2012 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Pfeffer - Wealth after the Great Recession - Who Lost, Who Recovered, and Why (92-12-15), 2012-2015 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Rothstein - The Labor Market in the Great Recession - What Role for the Supply Side (92-12-08), 2011-2014 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Sanchez - The Great Recession - Implications for Minority and Immigrant Communities (92-12-16), 2012-2014 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Schanzenbach - Understanding Food Insecurity During the Great Recession (92-12-09), 2011-2014 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Von Wachter - Is There a Cleansing Effect of Recessions - An Analysis of Employment Changes at the Industry and Firm Level (92-11-16), 2011-2015 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Immigration
    - Alba - New Immigrants in the Hudson Valley (88-05-16), 2005-2008 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Bean and Brown - Mexican Immigrant Group Incorporation (88-08-16), 2008-2010 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Bean - Immigration, Racial/Ethnic Diversity, and Multiracial Identification (88-01-11), 2001-2010 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
    - Bhagwati - Skilled Migration Today: Prospects, Problems, and Policies (88-05-01), 2004-2008 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Blau and Kahn - Immigration, Gender and Labor Market (88-04-02), 2003-2008 (Box 10, Folder 5-6)
    - Bretell, Reed-Danahay - Practicing Citizenship in a New City of Immigration - An Ethnographic Comparison of Asian Indians and Vietnamese (88-05-19), 2005-2010 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Brown - Intergenerational Spatial Assimilation Among the Descendants of Mexican Immigrants in Metropolitan Los Angeles (88-08-01), 2007-2010 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Cain and Bloemraad - Learning Civic Engagement: Political Socialization in Mexican Origin Families with Mixed Citizenship Status (88-06-08), 2005-2008 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Callahan and Muller - New Citizens in a New Century: Immigrant Students, Schools, and Teachers (88-09-01), 2008-2010 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Card and Raphael - Conference and Edited Volume on Poverty, Inequality and Immigration (88-11-03), 2011-2013 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Cho - Explaining Postsecondary Choices among Hispanic Adolescents (88-12-02), 2012-2014 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Cortina - The Schooling of Immigrants in New York (88-03-01), 2002-2006 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Coutin, Charcon, Lee and Ashar - Navigating Liminal Legalities Along Pathways to Citizenship - Immigrant Vulnerability and the Role of Mediating Institutions (88-14-06), 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Deaux - The Psychological Functions of Membership in Ethnically-Relevant Organizations (88-08-06), 2007-2009 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - DeParle - A Good Provider is One Who Leaves - Migration in the 21st Century (88-13-02), 2012-2014 (Box 21, Folder 5)